



# mahdi karimian

Date of birth: 11 Mar 1990 | Nationality: Iranian | Gender: Male

Phone number: (+39) 3516501015 (Mobile) | Email address:

mahdii.kariimiian@gmail.com | Address: Turin, Italy (Home)

#### ABOUT ME

I am currently focused on mastering front-end development, specifically learning JavaScript and various frameworks to create engaging digital experiences. I am eagerly awaiting an opportunity to expand my expertise, take on challenges, and continue growing.

## DIGITAL SKILLS

JavaScript | HTML | CSS | Tailwind | Bootstrap | Github | React Frame Work

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PERSIAN** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - CURRENT Tehran, Iran

#### **PODCAST CREATOR SELF-EMPLOYED**

This is a mythology-focused podcast that included humor and detailed information.

- Presented with a friendly and attractive tone
- quickly became one of the most popular podcasts in Iran, with more than 30,000 listeners.

This experience turned my attention to the details that attract the audience's attention. As I transitioned from the podcast to website development, I discovered similarities in connecting with the audience.

**Business or Sector** Arts, entertainment and recreation | **Department** ostooraakh podcast

2017 - 2020 Tehran, Iran

#### **EDITORIAL DIRECTOR** ALLAMEH TABATABAEI HIGH SCHOOL

I worked as the Editorial Director at the Content Production Department, where I had a diverse role such as:

- covering the news and activities and upload on the site.
- designing and implementing various festivals and competitions for students.

This position provided me with valuable insights into managing groups and resolving potential challenges between site designers and users. This experience enriched my perspective as I transitioned into front-end development.

## EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2016 - 2018 Tehran, Iran

STORYTELLING AND CREATIVE WRITING SKILLS Payame Noor University

2019 - 2023 Tehran, Iran

**TRANSLATION AND INTERPRETING** Payame Noor University

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# **PROJECTS**

2023 - CURRENT

**My Github Repositories** This is my GitHub profile, where you can find a collection of over 30 small projects primarily sourced from "frontendmentors.io." While these projects are one-page creations, they mirror the challenges encountered in real website development. Feel free to explore my repository to get a glimpse of my skills and passion for creating intuitive and interactive digital experiences.

Link <a href="https://github.com/Mahdii-Kariimiian">https://github.com/Mahdii-Kariimiian</a>